Yeah, they hate that.
(Leonard:)You know what, Sheldon is the
smartest person I have ever met.
(Leonard:)He's a little broken
and he needs me.
(Leonard:)I guess I need him, too.
(Arthur:)Why is that?
(Leonard:)Boy, you will not
let this go, will you?
Oh, geez.
(Arthur:)Another photo from Sheldon?
(Leonard:)No, I have to go pick him up.
(Leonard:)Bill Nye ditched him
at the smoothie place.
(Arthur:)He probably stole his wallet, too.
(Howard:)You know, if you guys are interested,
(Howard:)there's a technique
where I can take a lock of your hair,
(Howard:)refine it into carbon dust,
and use the hydraulic press at work
(Howard:)to turn it into a tiny little diamond
with your DNA in it.
Oh, that's amazing!
(Howard:)Yeah. See Bernie's engagement ring?
(Howard:)That came right off my mom's back.
(Bernadette:)He's kidding.
(Bernadette:)If that were true,
it'd be so much bigger.